Guide to the Records of the Communications Workers of America, Local 1150 WAG.059
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IX: Subject Files, 1941-1989
  - AT&T Financial Report, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - AT&T, Long Lines Dept., personnel charts, 1951 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - AT&T manual: Administrative Practices, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Attorney, 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - AUTW, Affiliation with CWA: promotional material, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - AUTW, Educational Dept., 1946 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - AUTW General Wage Case, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Bell Buster, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Bell Wringer, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Benefit Booklets, 1960-1976 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Blood Bank, 1955-1956, 1960-1966 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Blue Cross and Blue Shield, 1955-1969 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Catholic Communications Guild, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - City of Hope, 1961-1966, 1977, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - CLUW, 1979, 1981-1984 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Code of Conduct: Long Lines, U470 Form, etc., 1963, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Collins, Eleanore, 1960-1971 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Common Interest Forum, 1984-1987 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Communications Technicians, undated (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Community Relations Program, CWA, undated (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Company Restructure, Apr 1982 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Concerned Women Committee (CWC), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Concessions, 1980, 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Cornell University, NY State School of Industrial & Labor Relations, 1960-1970 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Craft Test (new), 1984 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - CWA Representation Map, undated (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Daily Work Log, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Defense Fund, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Demonstration Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Dental Plan, 1965-1969, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Dissident Publications, 1975, 1983, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - District 65, Bell Telephone Local, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Divestiture, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Domestic Violence, 1981-1984 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Drug Abuse, [1973] (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - EAP (Employee Assistance Program), 1981 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - EAP (Employee Assistance Program), 1984 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Easter Schedules, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Education Committee, 1979-1982 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Education Department, 1962-1963 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Employee Assistance Program, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Engineering Associates, qualifications for, etc., 1963-1966 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Environmental matters/working conditions, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Equal Access Campaign, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Equal Opportunity: Study of Bell System, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - FCC Public Inquiry, 1979, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Field Office, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Greater New York Fund, 1955-1959 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Grievance Procedures, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Grievance Reports, 1952-1954, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Grievance Reports, 1962-1964, 1966-1968 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Hard Core Program, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Health Plan, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - "Hi Mom" Project, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - "Hi Mom" Project, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - "Hi Mom" Project, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - "Hi Mom" Project, 1969-1972 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Hidden Camera Case, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Holiday Assignments, 1950-1976 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - "I'm Easy" Campaign, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - IOC, 1979, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - International Operating Center (IOC): Closing, 1982-1984 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Job Briefs, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Job Descriptions, 1944, 1952, 1982-1984 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Job Pressures Study Committee, CWA, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Job Security, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Labor Day, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Larson, Ella Jane, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - League for Industrial Democracy (L.I.C.), 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Legislative-Political, 1980-1983 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Life Insurance, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Life Membership Cards, 1968-1970 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Lincoln's Day Dinner, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Long Island Federation of Labor, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Management Rights, AT&T manual, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Manual Unit, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Maternity Disability Benefits, 1979, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Medical and Surgical Plan, 1955-1964 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Membership, 1966, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Membership records, misc., early 1950s, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Merger with Local 1101, proposed, undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Message Investigation Center (MIC) Report, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - MIC Job Preference Study, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Military information (& veterans' affairs), 1950-1968 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Military Pay Scale, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Minimum Wage, [1962] (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Mobilization, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - NLRB Cases, 1979, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - New Jersey: proposals for a separate local, etc., 1963, 1970-1981 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - New Jersey State Industrial Union Council, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - New Jersey State Industrial Union Council, 1979-1982 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - "News from Newark", 1965 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - New York City Central Labor Council, Community Services Committee, 1961-1967 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - New York City Central Labor Council, Project Rehab, 1959, 1963-1965, 1975-1977 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - NY State AFL-CIO, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - New York State Women's Conference, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Operation South America, CWA District 1, 1961-1967 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Organizing, 1962-1965, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Overseas Operations, 1959-1964, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Overtime, undated, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Overtime Equalization, 1952-1953 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Pension Fund, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Pension Plan, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Petition for R.N. on 24-hour duty, undated (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Plant Problems, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Plant Routines, 1945-1946 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Platelet Program, 1968, undated (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Promotions, 1953, undated (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Publicity, general, 1963-1968, 1977-1979, undated (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Quality of Work Life (QWL), 1981-1985 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Quality of Work Life (QWL): Minutes, 1981-1983 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Raffle, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Retired Members Club, 1976, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Safety: IOC Fire, 1967-1970, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Savings Plan, Bell System, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Seating Plan: Meetings, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Senate Committee on Labor-Management Relations, CWA testimony, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Seniority, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Solidarity Day, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Speak Out! Program, AT&T, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Statue of Liberty Restoration Project, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Stress, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Structure Review Committee, CWA Int'l, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Teamster Raid, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Teamsters Union (IBT), 1963 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Telecommunications Act of 1982 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Telecommunications International Union, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Telephoto Service, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Tours, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Traffic Petitions, 1966, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Traffic Section, 1959-1977 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Traffic Wage Case (National War Labor Board), 1945 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Training: Local Officers, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Training Programs, AT&T, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Training: Stewards, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Transit Strikes, 1965, 1976, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Tuberculosis, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Tuition Aid Plan, AT&T Long Lines Dept., 1962-1971 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Unification of CWA-CIO and TWOC-CIO: documents, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Uniform Operating Practice Manual, 1960-1963 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Union and Employee Assistance Committee on Domestic Violence, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Union Committee Against Secret Service Harrassment, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Union of Telephone Workers, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Union Purchasing Plan, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Union Family Action Program, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - United Fund of Greater New York, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - US Department of Labor, Long Lines Study: Preliminary Report, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - US Department of Labor, Long Lines Study: Appendix, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Upgrade and Transfer Plan, 1974, 1976, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Vacation, 1975, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - VDT's, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Wage Schedules, 1944, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Watts, Glenn, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Welfare Cases: Non-Financial, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Welfare cases: Financial Loans: A-H, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Welfare cases: Financial Loans: J-Z, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Welfare Committee: general, 1958-1961 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Welfare Committee:: loans, 1950-1953 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - White Plains: Organizing, 1963-1965 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - White Plains: Separate Local, 1970-1975 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Women's Issues, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1961, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Xavier Institute, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Series X: Mimeo File, 1944-1978
  - FFLTW, Traffic Branch 101, Bulletin Board Notices, 1944-1946 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Mimeo File, 1954-1955 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Mimeo File, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Mimeo File, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Mimeo File, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Mimeo File, 1959-1961 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Mimeo File, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Mimeo File, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Mimeo File, 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Mimeo File, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Mimeo File, 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Mimeo File, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Mimeo File, 1972-1974 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Mimeo File, 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Mimeo File, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Series XI: Telephone Tapes: Transcripts, 1967-1979
  - Telephone Tapes: transcripts, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Telephone Tapes: transcripts, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Telephone Tapes: transcripts, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Telephone Tapes: transcripts, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Telephone Tapes: transcripts, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Telephone Tapes: transcripts, Oct 1974-Sep 1976, 1977-1979 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Series XII: Newsletters, Bulletins, and Clippings, 1951-1989
  - Local 1150 Newsletter, working files: drafts, art work, notices, etc., 1957-1970s (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Local 1150 Newsletter, working files: corresp., etc., 1960s-1970s (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Local 1150, Administrative Section, Advocate (monthly bulletin), [1954-1958?] (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - CWA LL Bargaining Unit, Information Bulletin and Special Bulletin, 1960, 1964-1966 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - CWA LL Bargaining Unit, Information Bulletin and Special Bulletin, 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - CWA LL Bargaining Unit, Information Bulletin and Special Bulletin, 1970-1976, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - CWA Installation Bargaining Unit, Bargaining Reports, 1956-1958, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - CWA, Communication Allied Press Service: bulletins, 1964-1966 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - CWA, Memo to CWA Local Presidents, 1956-1958 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - CWA, Recent Important Labor Developments (with index), Jun 1951-Jul 1953 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - CWA Local 1150, Traffic Bulletins, 1980-1983 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Clippings, 1952, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1962-1963 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1966-1968 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1971-1977 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1980-1989 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Series XIII: Unprocessed Materials, 1950s-1980s
  - General Files: Arbitration Cases (Box 27)
  - General Files: Political Handbills (Box 28)
  - General Files: Correspondence (Box 29)
  - General Files: Financial Study and CWA Board Minutes (Box 30)
  - General Files: Contract Negotiations and Correspondence (Box 31)
  - General Files: Pamphlets, Newsreports and Bargaining Materials (Box 32)
  - General Files: Bargaining Material, Seniority Lists and Union Elections (Box 33)
  - General Files (Box 34)
  - General Files (Box 35)
  - General Files (Box 36)
  - General Files (Box 37)
  - Miscellaneous Grievances and Some General Files, 1960's-1980's (Box 38)
  - Miscellaneous Grievances and Strike Materials (Box 39)
  - Grievances: Administrative, National (Box 40)
  - Grievances: Traffic, National (Box 41)
  - Grievances: Traffic, Level Unknown (Box 42)
  - Grievances: Traffic, National (Box 43)
  - Grievances: Traffic, 1960-1969 (Box 44)
  - Grievances: Traffic, 1970-1979 (Box 45)
  - Grievances: Plant, Local (Box 46)
  - Grievances: Administrative, 1950-1959 (Box 47)
  - Grievances: Administrative, National (Box 48)
  - Grievances: Traffic, National (Box 49)
  - Grievances: Plant, National (Box 50)
  - Grievances: Administrative, National (Box 51)
  - Grievances: Traffic, National (Box 52)
  - Grievances: Miscellaneous Departments (Box 53)
  - Grievances: Traffic, 1940's-1950's (Box 54)
  - Grievances: Traffic, National (Box 55)
  - Grievances: Traffic, 1980-1989 (Box 56)
  - Grievances: Plant, 1980's (Box 57)
  - Grievances: Traffic, 1970's-1980's (Box 58)
  - Grievances: Traffic; Arranged Alphabetically by Name, 1978-1984 (Box 59)
  - Grievances: Miscellaneous Departments (Box 60)
  - Grievances: Administrative, National (Box 61)
  - Grievances: Miscellaneous Departments (Box 62)
  - Grievances: Administrative, Local (Box 63)
  - Grievances: Plant, National (Box 64)
  - Grievances: Miscellaneous Departments, 1980's (Box 65)
  - Grievances and Union Memos (Box 66)
  - Grievances: Plant and District (Box 67)
  - Grievances: Traffic, 1950-1959 (Box 68)
  - Grievances: Traffic, District (Box 69)
  - Grievances: Plant (Box 70)
  - Grievances: Plant, National, 1970's-1980's (Box 71)
  - Grievances: Administrative, Local (includes some general files and background material), 1960's-1980's (Box 72)
  - Grievances: Plant, National (Box 73)
  - Ephemera, 1987 (Box 77)
  - VHS tapes, 1990 (Box 77)
  - Unprocessed materials (Box 78)
  - Unprocessed Videos (Box 79)
- Series XIV: Photographs, 1940s-1980s
  Scope and Content Note
  Photographs in Box 74 are arranged in subject folders. Materials in boxes 75 and 76 are unprocessed.
  - Demonstrations -- Equal Rights Amendment (Richmond, Virginia, January 13, 1980(?)), 1963 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Demonstrations - "Gibson Girls" March - 1963 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Ephemera (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Group Portraits (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Meetings (8 x 10 prints) (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Meetings (3 x 5 snapshots and some matching negatives) (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous photographs and slides (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Portraits (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Social (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Surveillance By AT & T - 1963 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Welfare (Good and Welfare) (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Worksites (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Unprocessed 8x10 black and white prints and color slides, 1940s-1960s (Box 75)
  - Unprocessed 3 x 5 and 4 x 6 snapshots/prints and 35mm negatives, 1970s-1990s (Box 76)
  - Oversized Photographs (includes national conventions, meetings of longlines division), 1940s-1960s (Flat-file-folder 4, Tray 3, Box XOS002, Folder 1)
- Series XV: Archived Websites, February 2009-ongoing
  Communication Workers of America, Local 1150 is based in New York, NY, and represents landline technicians in the New York and New Jersey metropolitan area. The website contains union news and bargaining and contract documents.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
  Accruals
  New site crawls are accrued semiannually.
  Appraisal
  Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of http://cwa1150.com/ in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.